{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "(0, -1)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by 2\n2(x + 4y) \u003d 2(-4)\n2x + 8y \u003d -8\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n7y \u003d -7\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -7 / 7 \u003d -1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n2x + y \u003d -1\n2x + (-1) \u003d -1\n2x + -1 \u003d -1\n2x \u003d -1 + 1 \u003d 0\nx \u003d 0 / 2 \u003d 0", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + y \u003d -1\nx + 4y \u003d -4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, 0)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by -5\n-5(x + y) \u003d -5(4)\n-5x - 5y \u003d -20\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-7y \u003d 0\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 0 / -7 \u003d 0\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n-5x + 2y \u003d -20\n-5x + 2(0) \u003d -20\n-5x + 0 \u003d -20\n-5x \u003d -20 - 0 \u003d -20\nx \u003d -20 / -5 \u003d 4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + y \u003d 4\n-5x + 2y \u003d -20", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, 2)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\nx + y \u003d 7\nx + y \u003d -1-4y \u003d -8\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -8 / -4 \u003d 2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\nx + 5y \u003d 7\nx + 5(2) \u003d 7\nx + 10 \u003d 7x \u003d 7 - 10 \u003d -3\nx \u003d -3 / 1 \u003d -3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + 5y \u003d 7\nx + y \u003d -1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-5, -3)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\nx + y \u003d -8\nx - 3y \u003d 4-4y \u003d 12\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 12 / -4 \u003d -3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\nx + y \u003d -8\nx + (-3) \u003d -8\nx + -3 \u003d -8x \u003d -8 + 3 \u003d -5\nx \u003d -5 / 1 \u003d -5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + y \u003d -8\nx - 3y \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, -3)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n2x + 10y \u003d -1\n10x + y \u003d 78x \u003d 8\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d 8 / 8 \u003d 1\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n2x + y \u003d -1\n2(1) + y \u003d -1\ny + 2 \u003d -1\ny \u003d -1 - 2 \u003d -3\ny \u003d -3 / 1 \u003d -3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + y \u003d -1\n10x + y \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5, -4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(2x + y) \u003d 4(6)\n8x + 4y \u003d 24\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable y\n13x \u003d 65\nSolve for x in the new equation\nx \u003d 65 / 13 \u003d 5\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n-5x + 4y \u003d -41\n-5(5) + 4y \u003d -41\n4y + -25 \u003d -41\n4y \u003d -41 + 25 \u003d -16\ny \u003d -16 / 4 \u003d -4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + y \u003d 6\n-5x + 4y \u003d -41", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(0, 1)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(3x + 3y) \u003d 3(3)\n9x + 9y \u003d 9\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n8y \u003d 8\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 8 / 8 \u003d 1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n9x + y \u003d 1\n9x + (1) \u003d 1\n9x + 1 \u003d 1\n9x \u003d 1 - 1 \u003d 0\nx \u003d 0 / 9 \u003d 0", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 3y \u003d 3\n9x + y \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-4, 4)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n3x + 4y \u003d 0\n4x + 3y \u003d -4x \u003d -4\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -4 / 1 \u003d -4\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n3x + 3y \u003d 0\n3(-4) + 3y \u003d 0\n3y + -12 \u003d 0\n3y \u003d 0 + 12 \u003d 12\ny \u003d 12 / 3 \u003d 4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 3y \u003d 0\n4x + 3y \u003d -4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, 2)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n4x + 4y \u003d 18\n4x + 4y \u003d 243y \u003d 6\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 6 / 3 \u003d 2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x + y \u003d 18\n4x + (2) \u003d 18\n4x + 2 \u003d 184x \u003d 18 - 2 \u003d 16\nx \u003d 16 / 4 \u003d 4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + y \u003d 18\n4x + 4y \u003d 24", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3, -3)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(3x + 3y) \u003d 4(0)\n12x + 12y \u003d 0\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n11y \u003d -33\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -33 / 11 \u003d -3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n12x + y \u003d 33\n12x + (-3) \u003d 33\n12x + -3 \u003d 33\n12x \u003d 33 + 3 \u003d 36\nx \u003d 36 / 12 \u003d 3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 3y \u003d 0\n12x + y \u003d 33", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, 5)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 5\n5(2x + 2y) \u003d 5(6)\n10x + 10y \u003d 30\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n15y \u003d 75\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 75 / 15 \u003d 5\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n10x - 5y \u003d -45\n10x - 5(5) \u003d -45\n10x + -25 \u003d -45\n10x \u003d -45 + 25 \u003d -20\nx \u003d -20 / 10 \u003d -2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 2y \u003d 6\n10x - 5y \u003d -45", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, -1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n2x + 2y \u003d -1\n2x + y \u003d 1-2y \u003d 2\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 2 / -2 \u003d -1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n2x + 3y \u003d -1\n2x + 3(-1) \u003d -1\n2x + -3 \u003d -12x \u003d -1 + 3 \u003d 2\nx \u003d 2 / 2 \u003d 1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 3y \u003d -1\n2x + y \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, -4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by -4\n-4(-x + 4y) \u003d -4(-14)\n4x - 16y \u003d 56\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-24y \u003d 96\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 96 / -24 \u003d -4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x + 8y \u003d -40\n4x + 8(-4) \u003d -40\n4x + -32 \u003d -40\n4x \u003d -40 + 32 \u003d -8\nx \u003d -8 / 4 \u003d -2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-x + 4y \u003d -14\n4x + 8y \u003d -40", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(0, -5)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 2\n2(3x + 4y) \u003d 2(-20)\n6x + 8y \u003d -40\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable y\n10x \u003d 0\nSolve for x in the new equation\nx \u003d 0 / 10 \u003d 0\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n-4x + 8y \u003d -40\n-4(0) + 8y \u003d -40\n8y + 0 \u003d -40\n8y \u003d -40 - 0 \u003d -40\ny \u003d -40 / 8 \u003d -5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 4y \u003d -20\n-4x + 8y \u003d -40", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-5, 4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(3x - y) \u003d 4(-19)\n12x - 4y \u003d -76\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-2y \u003d -8\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -8 / -2 \u003d 4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n12x - 2y \u003d -68\n12x - 2(4) \u003d -68\n12x + -8 \u003d -68\n12x \u003d -68 + 8 \u003d -60\nx \u003d -60 / 12 \u003d -5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x - y \u003d -19\n12x - 2y \u003d -68", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, -3)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\nx + y \u003d -1\nx + 5y \u003d -134y \u003d -12\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -12 / 4 \u003d -3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\nx + y \u003d -1\nx + (-3) \u003d -1\nx + -3 \u003d -1x \u003d -1 + 3 \u003d 2\nx \u003d 2 / 1 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + y \u003d -1\nx + 5y \u003d -13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, 0)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(3x + 3y) \u003d 4(-6)\n12x + 12y \u003d -24\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable y\n14x \u003d -28\nSolve for x in the new equation\nx \u003d -28 / 14 \u003d -2\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n-2x + 12y \u003d 4\n-2(-2) + 12y \u003d 4\n12y + 4 \u003d 4\n12y \u003d 4 - 4 \u003d 0\ny \u003d 0 / 12 \u003d 0", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 3y \u003d -6\n-2x + 12y \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, 4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by -1\n-1(-3x + 3y) \u003d -1(9)\n3x - 3y \u003d -9\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-4y \u003d -16\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -16 / -4 \u003d 4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x + y \u003d 7\n3x + (4) \u003d 7\n3x + 4 \u003d 7\n3x \u003d 7 - 4 \u003d 3\nx \u003d 3 / 3 \u003d 1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + y \u003d 7\n-3x + 3y \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-4, 3)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 2\n2(2x + 5y) \u003d 2(7)\n4x + 10y \u003d 14\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n14y \u003d 42\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 42 / 14 \u003d 3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x - 4y \u003d -28\n4x - 4(3) \u003d -28\n4x + -12 \u003d -28\n4x \u003d -28 + 12 \u003d -16\nx \u003d -16 / 4 \u003d -4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 5y \u003d 7\n4x - 4y \u003d -28", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, 2)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n-2x - 2y \u003d 10\n-2x + 8y \u003d 226y \u003d 12\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 12 / 6 \u003d 2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n-2x + 2y \u003d 10\n-2x + 2(2) \u003d 10\n-2x + 4 \u003d 10-2x \u003d 10 - 4 \u003d 6\nx \u003d 6 / -2 \u003d -3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-2x + 2y \u003d 10\n-2x + 8y \u003d 22", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, 2)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(4x - y) \u003d 3(14)\n12x - 3y \u003d 42\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n1y \u003d 2\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 2 / 1 \u003d 2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n12x - 4y \u003d 40\n12x - 4(2) \u003d 40\n12x + -8 \u003d 40\n12x \u003d 40 + 8 \u003d 48\nx \u003d 48 / 12 \u003d 4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x - y \u003d 14\n12x - 4y \u003d 40", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, 3)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(x + y) \u003d 3(0)\n3x + 3y \u003d 0\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n5y \u003d 15\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 15 / 5 \u003d 3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x - 2y \u003d -15\n3x - 2(3) \u003d -15\n3x + -6 \u003d -15\n3x \u003d -15 + 6 \u003d -9\nx \u003d -9 / 3 \u003d -3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + y \u003d 0\n3x - 2y \u003d -15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3, -4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by -2\n-2(x + 10y) \u003d -2(-37)\n-2x - 20y \u003d 74\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-22y \u003d 88\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 88 / -22 \u003d -4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n-2x + 2y \u003d -14\n-2x + 2(-4) \u003d -14\n-2x + -8 \u003d -14\n-2x \u003d -14 + 8 \u003d -6\nx \u003d -6 / -2 \u003d 3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-2x + 2y \u003d -14\nx + 10y \u003d -37", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, 0)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 2\n2(4x - 2y) \u003d 2(8)\n8x - 4y \u003d 16\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n1y \u003d 0\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 0 / 1 \u003d 0\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n8x - 5y \u003d 16\n8x - 5(0) \u003d 16\n8x + 0 \u003d 16\n8x \u003d 16 - 0 \u003d 16\nx \u003d 16 / 8 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x - 2y \u003d 8\n8x - 5y \u003d 16", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5, 5)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n-2x - 3y \u003d 0\n-3x + 2y \u003d -5-x \u003d -5\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -5 / -1 \u003d 5\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n-2x + 2y \u003d 0\n-2(5) + 2y \u003d 0\n2y + -10 \u003d 0\n2y \u003d 0 + 10 \u003d 10\ny \u003d 10 / 2 \u003d 5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-2x + 2y \u003d 0\n-3x + 2y \u003d -5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, 2)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by -2\n-2(2x + 4y) \u003d -2(12)\n-4x - 8y \u003d -24\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-24y \u003d -48\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -48 / -24 \u003d 2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n-4x + 16y \u003d 24\n-4x + 16(2) \u003d 24\n-4x + 32 \u003d 24\n-4x \u003d 24 - 32 \u003d -8\nx \u003d -8 / -4 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 4y \u003d 12\n-4x + 16y \u003d 24", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-5, -5)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n4x + 4y \u003d -35\n4x - 3y \u003d -5-6y \u003d 30\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 30 / -6 \u003d -5\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x + 3y \u003d -35\n4x + 3(-5) \u003d -35\n4x + -15 \u003d -354x \u003d -35 + 15 \u003d -20\nx \u003d -20 / 4 \u003d -5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + 3y \u003d -35\n4x - 3y \u003d -5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, 5)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by -2\n-2(x + 6y) \u003d -2(32)\n-2x - 12y \u003d -64\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-14y \u003d -70\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -70 / -14 \u003d 5\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n-2x + 2y \u003d 6\n-2x + 2(5) \u003d 6\n-2x + 10 \u003d 6\n-2x \u003d 6 - 10 \u003d -4\nx \u003d -4 / -2 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-2x + 2y \u003d 6\nx + 6y \u003d 32", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, -2)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n4x + 20y \u003d 14\n20x + y \u003d 7816x \u003d 64\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d 64 / 16 \u003d 4\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n4x + y \u003d 14\n4(4) + y \u003d 14\ny + 16 \u003d 14\ny \u003d 14 - 16 \u003d -2\ny \u003d -2 / 1 \u003d -2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + y \u003d 14\n20x + y \u003d 78", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5, -1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n5x + 3y \u003d 24\n3x + y \u003d 14-2x \u003d -10\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -10 / -2 \u003d 5\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n5x + y \u003d 24\n5(5) + y \u003d 24\ny + 25 \u003d 24\ny \u003d 24 - 25 \u003d -1\ny \u003d -1 / 1 \u003d -1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n5x + y \u003d 24\n3x + y \u003d 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, 0)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 5\n5(4x + y) \u003d 5(8)\n20x + 5y \u003d 40\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n3y \u003d 0\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 0 / 3 \u003d 0\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n20x + 2y \u003d 40\n20x + 2(0) \u003d 40\n20x + 0 \u003d 40\n20x \u003d 40 - 0 \u003d 40\nx \u003d 40 / 20 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + y \u003d 8\n20x + 2y \u003d 40", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, -2)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 2\n2(2x + 4y) \u003d 2(-6)\n4x + 8y \u003d -12\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n7y \u003d -14\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -14 / 7 \u003d -2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x + y \u003d 2\n4x + (-2) \u003d 2\n4x + -2 \u003d 2\n4x \u003d 2 + 2 \u003d 4\nx \u003d 4 / 4 \u003d 1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 4y \u003d -6\n4x + y \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, -1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\nx - 4y \u003d 1\n-4x + y \u003d -9-5x \u003d -10\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -10 / -5 \u003d 2\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\nx + y \u003d 1\n(2) + y \u003d 1\ny + 2 \u003d 1\ny \u003d 1 - 2 \u003d -1\ny \u003d -1 / 1 \u003d -1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + y \u003d 1\n-4x + y \u003d -9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, 1)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 5\n5(3x - y) \u003d 5(5)\n15x - 5y \u003d 25\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-2y \u003d -2\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -2 / -2 \u003d 1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n15x - 3y \u003d 27\n15x - 3(1) \u003d 27\n15x + -3 \u003d 27\n15x \u003d 27 + 3 \u003d 30\nx \u003d 30 / 15 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x - y \u003d 5\n15x - 3y \u003d 27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, -4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(4x - 2y) \u003d 3(16)\n12x - 6y \u003d 48\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-7y \u003d 28\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 28 / -7 \u003d -4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n12x + y \u003d 20\n12x + (-4) \u003d 20\n12x + -4 \u003d 20\n12x \u003d 20 + 4 \u003d 24\nx \u003d 24 / 12 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x - 2y \u003d 16\n12x + y \u003d 20", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, -3)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by 4\n4(x + 4y) \u003d 4(-11)\n4x + 16y \u003d -44\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n14y \u003d -42\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -42 / 14 \u003d -3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x + 2y \u003d -2\n4x + 2(-3) \u003d -2\n4x + -6 \u003d -2\n4x \u003d -2 + 6 \u003d 4\nx \u003d 4 / 4 \u003d 1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + 2y \u003d -2\nx + 4y \u003d -11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, 5)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n2x + 6y \u003d 4\n6x + 2y \u003d -84x \u003d -12\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -12 / 4 \u003d -3\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n2x + 2y \u003d 4\n2(-3) + 2y \u003d 4\n2y + -6 \u003d 4\n2y \u003d 4 + 6 \u003d 10\ny \u003d 10 / 2 \u003d 5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 2y \u003d 4\n6x + 2y \u003d -8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5, -2)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(x + 2y) \u003d 4(1)\n4x + 8y \u003d 4\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n2y \u003d -4\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -4 / 2 \u003d -2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x + 6y \u003d 8\n4x + 6(-2) \u003d 8\n4x + -12 \u003d 8\n4x \u003d 8 + 12 \u003d 20\nx \u003d 20 / 4 \u003d 5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + 2y \u003d 1\n4x + 6y \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, 3)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n2x - 4y \u003d 17\n-4x + 3y \u003d -7-6x \u003d -24\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -24 / -6 \u003d 4\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n2x + 3y \u003d 17\n2(4) + 3y \u003d 17\n3y + 8 \u003d 17\n3y \u003d 17 - 8 \u003d 9\ny \u003d 9 / 3 \u003d 3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 3y \u003d 17\n-4x + 3y \u003d -7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, 3)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(x + 4y) \u003d 4(13)\n4x + 16y \u003d 52\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n18y \u003d 54\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 54 / 18 \u003d 3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x - 2y \u003d -2\n4x - 2(3) \u003d -2\n4x + -6 \u003d -2\n4x \u003d -2 + 6 \u003d 4\nx \u003d 4 / 4 \u003d 1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + 4y \u003d 13\n4x - 2y \u003d -2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3, 0)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 2\n2(x + 4y) \u003d 2(3)\n2x + 8y \u003d 6\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n5y \u003d 0\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 0 / 5 \u003d 0\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n2x + 3y \u003d 6\n2x + 3(0) \u003d 6\n2x + 0 \u003d 6\n2x \u003d 6 - 0 \u003d 6\nx \u003d 6 / 2 \u003d 3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + 4y \u003d 3\n2x + 3y \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, -4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by -2\n-2(x + y) \u003d -2(0)\n-2x - 2y \u003d 0\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-5y \u003d 20\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 20 / -5 \u003d -4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n-2x + 3y \u003d -20\n-2x + 3(-4) \u003d -20\n-2x + -12 \u003d -20\n-2x \u003d -20 + 12 \u003d -8\nx \u003d -8 / -2 \u003d 4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + y \u003d 0\n-2x + 3y \u003d -20", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3, -1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n-2x - 2y \u003d -9\n-2x + 9y \u003d -156y \u003d -6\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -6 / 6 \u003d -1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n-2x + 3y \u003d -9\n-2x + 3(-1) \u003d -9\n-2x + -3 \u003d -9-2x \u003d -9 + 3 \u003d -6\nx \u003d -6 / -2 \u003d 3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-2x + 3y \u003d -9\n-2x + 9y \u003d -15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, -4)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n4x + 12y \u003d -28\n12x + 4y \u003d -528x \u003d -24\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -24 / 8 \u003d -3\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n4x + 4y \u003d -28\n4(-3) + 4y \u003d -28\n4y + -12 \u003d -28\n4y \u003d -28 + 12 \u003d -16\ny \u003d -16 / 4 \u003d -4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + 4y \u003d -28\n12x + 4y \u003d -52", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, 4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 5\n5(x + y) \u003d 5(6)\n5x + 5y \u003d 30\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n8y \u003d 32\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 32 / 8 \u003d 4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n5x - 3y \u003d -2\n5x - 3(4) \u003d -2\n5x + -12 \u003d -2\n5x \u003d -2 + 12 \u003d 10\nx \u003d 10 / 5 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + y \u003d 6\n5x - 3y \u003d -2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, -4)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n3x + 3y \u003d -25\n3x - 3y \u003d 3-7y \u003d 28\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 28 / -7 \u003d -4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x + 4y \u003d -25\n3x + 4(-4) \u003d -25\n3x + -16 \u003d -253x \u003d -25 + 16 \u003d -9\nx \u003d -9 / 3 \u003d -3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 4y \u003d -25\n3x - 3y \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-1, 1)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(x - 2y) \u003d 3(-3)\n3x - 6y \u003d -9\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-y \u003d -1\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -1 / -1 \u003d 1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x - 5y \u003d -8\n3x - 5(1) \u003d -8\n3x + -5 \u003d -8\n3x \u003d -8 + 5 \u003d -3\nx \u003d -3 / 3 \u003d -1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx - 2y \u003d -3\n3x - 5y \u003d -8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5, 2)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by 3\n3(x + 12y) \u003d 3(29)\n3x + 36y \u003d 87\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n33y \u003d 66\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 66 / 33 \u003d 2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x + 3y \u003d 21\n3x + 3(2) \u003d 21\n3x + 6 \u003d 21\n3x \u003d 21 - 6 \u003d 15\nx \u003d 15 / 3 \u003d 5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 3y \u003d 21\nx + 12y \u003d 29", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, 0)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(-x + 4y) \u003d 4(3)\n-4x + 16y \u003d 12\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n4y \u003d 0\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 0 / 4 \u003d 0\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n-4x + 12y \u003d 12\n-4x + 12(0) \u003d 12\n-4x + 0 \u003d 12\n-4x \u003d 12 - 0 \u003d 12\nx \u003d 12 / -4 \u003d -3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-x + 4y \u003d 3\n-4x + 12y \u003d 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, 1)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by -1\n-1(-x + 3y) \u003d -1(6)\nx - 3y \u003d -6\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-4y \u003d -4\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -4 / -4 \u003d 1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\nx + y \u003d -2\nx + (1) \u003d -2\nx + 1 \u003d -2\nx \u003d -2 - 1 \u003d -3\nx \u003d -3 / 1 \u003d -3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + y \u003d -2\n-x + 3y \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, 5)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n3x + 6y \u003d -1\n6x + y \u003d -73x \u003d -6\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -6 / 3 \u003d -2\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n3x + y \u003d -1\n3(-2) + y \u003d -1\ny + -6 \u003d -1\ny \u003d -1 + 6 \u003d 5\ny \u003d 5 / 1 \u003d 5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + y \u003d -1\n6x + y \u003d -7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, 5)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 2\n2(3x + 3y) \u003d 2(9)\n6x + 6y \u003d 18\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable y\n4x \u003d -8\nSolve for x in the new equation\nx \u003d -8 / 4 \u003d -2\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n2x + 6y \u003d 26\n2(-2) + 6y \u003d 26\n6y + -4 \u003d 26\n6y \u003d 26 + 4 \u003d 30\ny \u003d 30 / 6 \u003d 5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 3y \u003d 9\n2x + 6y \u003d 26", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-1, -1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n2x + 2y \u003d -7\n2x + 4y \u003d -6-y \u003d 1\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 1 / -1 \u003d -1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n2x + 5y \u003d -7\n2x + 5(-1) \u003d -7\n2x + -5 \u003d -72x \u003d -7 + 5 \u003d -2\nx \u003d -2 / 2 \u003d -1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 5y \u003d -7\n2x + 4y \u003d -6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-5, 2)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by -1\n-1(-5x + 12y) \u003d -1(49)\n5x - 12y \u003d -49\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-16y \u003d -32\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -32 / -16 \u003d 2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n5x + 4y \u003d -17\n5x + 4(2) \u003d -17\n5x + 8 \u003d -17\n5x \u003d -17 - 8 \u003d -25\nx \u003d -25 / 5 \u003d -5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n5x + 4y \u003d -17\n-5x + 12y \u003d 49", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, -3)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by 4\n4(x + 2y) \u003d 4(-2)\n4x + 8y \u003d -8\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n7y \u003d -21\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -21 / 7 \u003d -3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x + y \u003d 13\n4x + (-3) \u003d 13\n4x + -3 \u003d 13\n4x \u003d 13 + 3 \u003d 16\nx \u003d 16 / 4 \u003d 4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + y \u003d 13\nx + 2y \u003d -2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, 5)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n2x + 2y \u003d -9\n2x - 4y \u003d -24-3y \u003d -15\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -15 / -3 \u003d 5\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n2x - y \u003d -9\n2x - (5) \u003d -9\n2x + -5 \u003d -92x \u003d -9 + 5 \u003d -4\nx \u003d -4 / 2 \u003d -2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x - y \u003d -9\n2x - 4y \u003d -24", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, -5)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n-2x + 2y \u003d -9\n2x + 3y \u003d -214x \u003d -12\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -12 / 4 \u003d -3\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n-2x + 3y \u003d -9\n-2(-3) + 3y \u003d -9\n3y + 6 \u003d -9\n3y \u003d -9 - 6 \u003d -15\ny \u003d -15 / 3 \u003d -5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-2x + 3y \u003d -9\n2x + 3y \u003d -21", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-5, -3)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(4x + 5y) \u003d 3(-35)\n12x + 15y \u003d -105\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n17y \u003d -51\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -51 / 17 \u003d -3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n12x - 2y \u003d -54\n12x - 2(-3) \u003d -54\n12x + 6 \u003d -54\n12x \u003d -54 - 6 \u003d -60\nx \u003d -60 / 12 \u003d -5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + 5y \u003d -35\n12x - 2y \u003d -54", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3, 5)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 2\n2(3x + 3y) \u003d 2(24)\n6x + 6y \u003d 48\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable y\n4x \u003d 12\nSolve for x in the new equation\nx \u003d 12 / 4 \u003d 3\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n2x + 6y \u003d 36\n2(3) + 6y \u003d 36\n6y + 6 \u003d 36\n6y \u003d 36 - 6 \u003d 30\ny \u003d 30 / 6 \u003d 5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 3y \u003d 24\n2x + 6y \u003d 36", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-5, -4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by 2\n2(x + 6y) \u003d 2(-29)\n2x + 12y \u003d -58\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n10y \u003d -40\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -40 / 10 \u003d -4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n2x + 2y \u003d -18\n2x + 2(-4) \u003d -18\n2x + -8 \u003d -18\n2x \u003d -18 + 8 \u003d -10\nx \u003d -10 / 2 \u003d -5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 2y \u003d -18\nx + 6y \u003d -29", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-4, -2)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 5\n5(4x + 4y) \u003d 5(-24)\n20x + 20y \u003d -120\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n19y \u003d -38\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -38 / 19 \u003d -2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n20x + y \u003d -82\n20x + (-2) \u003d -82\n20x + -2 \u003d -82\n20x \u003d -82 + 2 \u003d -80\nx \u003d -80 / 20 \u003d -4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + 4y \u003d -24\n20x + y \u003d -82", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3, -1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n3x + 4y \u003d 8\n4x + y \u003d 11x \u003d 3\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d 3 / 1 \u003d 3\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n3x + y \u003d 8\n3(3) + y \u003d 8\ny + 9 \u003d 8\ny \u003d 8 - 9 \u003d -1\ny \u003d -1 / 1 \u003d -1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + y \u003d 8\n4x + y \u003d 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, 5)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by -1\n-1(-x + 20y) \u003d -1(98)\nx - 20y \u003d -98\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-24y \u003d -120\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -120 / -24 \u003d 5\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\nx + 4y \u003d 22\nx + 4(5) \u003d 22\nx + 20 \u003d 22\nx \u003d 22 - 20 \u003d 2\nx \u003d 2 / 1 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + 4y \u003d 22\n-x + 20y \u003d 98", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, -1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n4x - 4y \u003d -13\n-4x + y \u003d 11-8x \u003d 24\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d 24 / -8 \u003d -3\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n4x + y \u003d -13\n4(-3) + y \u003d -13\ny + -12 \u003d -13\ny \u003d -13 + 12 \u003d -1\ny \u003d -1 / 1 \u003d -1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + y \u003d -13\n-4x + y \u003d 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3, -1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n2x + 2y \u003d 8\n2x - 3y \u003d 9-y \u003d 1\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 1 / -1 \u003d -1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n2x - 2y \u003d 8\n2x - 2(-1) \u003d 8\n2x + 2 \u003d 82x \u003d 8 - 2 \u003d 6\nx \u003d 6 / 2 \u003d 3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x - 2y \u003d 8\n2x - 3y \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5, -1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n5x + y \u003d 23\nx + 2y \u003d 3-4x \u003d -20\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -20 / -4 \u003d 5\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n5x + 2y \u003d 23\n5(5) + 2y \u003d 23\n2y + 25 \u003d 23\n2y \u003d 23 - 25 \u003d -2\ny \u003d -2 / 2 \u003d -1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n5x + 2y \u003d 23\nx + 2y \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, -4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 5\n5(4x + 3y) \u003d 5(-8)\n20x + 15y \u003d -40\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable y\n25x \u003d 25\nSolve for x in the new equation\nx \u003d 25 / 25 \u003d 1\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n-5x + 15y \u003d -65\n-5(1) + 15y \u003d -65\n15y + -5 \u003d -65\n15y \u003d -65 + 5 \u003d -60\ny \u003d -60 / 15 \u003d -4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + 3y \u003d -8\n-5x + 15y \u003d -65", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(0, 5)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by -1\n-1(-3x + 5y) \u003d -1(25)\n3x - 5y \u003d -25\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-6y \u003d -30\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -30 / -6 \u003d 5\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x + y \u003d 5\n3x + (5) \u003d 5\n3x + 5 \u003d 5\n3x \u003d 5 - 5 \u003d 0\nx \u003d 0 / 3 \u003d 0", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + y \u003d 5\n-3x + 5y \u003d 25", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-1, 0)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(3x + y) \u003d 4(-3)\n12x + 4y \u003d -12\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n9y \u003d 0\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 0 / 9 \u003d 0\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n12x - 5y \u003d -12\n12x - 5(0) \u003d -12\n12x + 0 \u003d -12\n12x \u003d -12 - 0 \u003d -12\nx \u003d -12 / 12 \u003d -1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + y \u003d -3\n12x - 5y \u003d -12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, 0)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\nx + y \u003d 2\nx - 4y \u003d 2-5y \u003d 0\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 0 / -5 \u003d 0\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\nx + y \u003d 2\nx + (0) \u003d 2\nx + 0 \u003d 2x \u003d 2 - 0 \u003d 2\nx \u003d 2 / 1 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + y \u003d 2\nx - 4y \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, 0)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 5\n5(3x + y) \u003d 5(6)\n15x + 5y \u003d 30\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n10y \u003d 0\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 0 / 10 \u003d 0\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n15x - 5y \u003d 30\n15x - 5(0) \u003d 30\n15x + 0 \u003d 30\n15x \u003d 30 - 0 \u003d 30\nx \u003d 30 / 15 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + y \u003d 6\n15x - 5y \u003d 30", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-1, 5)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n4x + y \u003d 11\nx + 3y \u003d 14-3x \u003d 3\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d 3 / -3 \u003d -1\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n4x + 3y \u003d 11\n4(-1) + 3y \u003d 11\n3y + -4 \u003d 11\n3y \u003d 11 + 4 \u003d 15\ny \u003d 15 / 3 \u003d 5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + 3y \u003d 11\nx + 3y \u003d 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, -3)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\nx + y \u003d -15\nx + 8y \u003d -274y \u003d -12\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -12 / 4 \u003d -3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\nx + 4y \u003d -15\nx + 4(-3) \u003d -15\nx + -12 \u003d -15x \u003d -15 + 12 \u003d -3\nx \u003d -3 / 1 \u003d -3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + 4y \u003d -15\nx + 8y \u003d -27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, -3)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the second equation by -1\n-1(-4x + 2y) \u003d -1(-14)\n4x - 2y \u003d 14\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-3y \u003d 9\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 9 / -3 \u003d -3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x + y \u003d 5\n4x + (-3) \u003d 5\n4x + -3 \u003d 5\n4x \u003d 5 + 3 \u003d 8\nx \u003d 8 / 4 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + y \u003d 5\n-4x + 2y \u003d -14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, 4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(2x + 4y) \u003d 4(12)\n8x + 16y \u003d 48\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n20y \u003d 80\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 80 / 20 \u003d 4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n8x - 4y \u003d -32\n8x - 4(4) \u003d -32\n8x + -16 \u003d -32\n8x \u003d -32 + 16 \u003d -16\nx \u003d -16 / 8 \u003d -2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 4y \u003d 12\n8x - 4y \u003d -32", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5, 3)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n3x + 3y \u003d 18\n3x + 3y \u003d 242y \u003d 6\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 6 / 2 \u003d 3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x + y \u003d 18\n3x + (3) \u003d 18\n3x + 3 \u003d 183x \u003d 18 - 3 \u003d 15\nx \u003d 15 / 3 \u003d 5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + y \u003d 18\n3x + 3y \u003d 24", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, -5)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(3x + 4y) \u003d 4(-26)\n12x + 16y \u003d -104\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable y\n17x \u003d -34\nSolve for x in the new equation\nx \u003d -34 / 17 \u003d -2\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n-5x + 16y \u003d -70\n-5(-2) + 16y \u003d -70\n16y + 10 \u003d -70\n16y \u003d -70 - 10 \u003d -80\ny \u003d -80 / 16 \u003d -5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 4y \u003d -26\n-5x + 16y \u003d -70", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, 5)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n-2x + 2y \u003d 9\n2x + y \u003d 14x \u003d -8\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -8 / 4 \u003d -2\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n-2x + y \u003d 9\n-2(-2) + y \u003d 9\ny + 4 \u003d 9\ny \u003d 9 - 4 \u003d 5\ny \u003d 5 / 1 \u003d 5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-2x + y \u003d 9\n2x + y \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, 0)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 5\n5(3x - y) \u003d 5(-6)\n15x - 5y \u003d -30\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-3y \u003d 0\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 0 / -3 \u003d 0\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n15x - 2y \u003d -30\n15x - 2(0) \u003d -30\n15x + 0 \u003d -30\n15x \u003d -30 - 0 \u003d -30\nx \u003d -30 / 15 \u003d -2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x - y \u003d -6\n15x - 2y \u003d -30", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-1, -3)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\nx + y \u003d -4\nx + 2y \u003d -71y \u003d -3\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -3 / 1 \u003d -3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\nx + y \u003d -4\nx + (-3) \u003d -4\nx + -3 \u003d -4x \u003d -4 + 3 \u003d -1\nx \u003d -1 / 1 \u003d -1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + y \u003d -4\nx + 2y \u003d -7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, -1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n3x + 3y \u003d 13\n3x + 4y \u003d 85y \u003d -5\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -5 / 5 \u003d -1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x - y \u003d 13\n3x - (-1) \u003d 13\n3x + 1 \u003d 133x \u003d 13 - 1 \u003d 12\nx \u003d 12 / 3 \u003d 4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x - y \u003d 13\n3x + 4y \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, -1)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(x + 4y) \u003d 4(-3)\n4x + 16y \u003d -12\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n17y \u003d -17\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -17 / 17 \u003d -1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x - y \u003d 5\n4x - (-1) \u003d 5\n4x + 1 \u003d 5\n4x \u003d 5 - 1 \u003d 4\nx \u003d 4 / 4 \u003d 1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + 4y \u003d -3\n4x - y \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, 1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n4x + 8y \u003d -11\n8x + y \u003d -234x \u003d -12\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -12 / 4 \u003d -3\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n4x + y \u003d -11\n4(-3) + y \u003d -11\ny + -12 \u003d -11\ny \u003d -11 + 12 \u003d 1\ny \u003d 1 / 1 \u003d 1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + y \u003d -11\n8x + y \u003d -23", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, -4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(3x + y) \u003d 3(8)\n9x + 3y \u003d 24\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-y \u003d 4\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 4 / -1 \u003d -4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n9x + 4y \u003d 20\n9x + 4(-4) \u003d 20\n9x + -16 \u003d 20\n9x \u003d 20 + 16 \u003d 36\nx \u003d 36 / 9 \u003d 4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + y \u003d 8\n9x + 4y \u003d 20", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, 2)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(4x + y) \u003d 3(-6)\n12x + 3y \u003d -18\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n6y \u003d 12\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 12 / 6 \u003d 2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n12x - 3y \u003d -30\n12x - 3(2) \u003d -30\n12x + -6 \u003d -30\n12x \u003d -30 + 6 \u003d -24\nx \u003d -24 / 12 \u003d -2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + y \u003d -6\n12x - 3y \u003d -30", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3, -4)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n4x + 4y \u003d -8\n4x \u003d -121y \u003d -4\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -4 / 1 \u003d -4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n4x - y \u003d -8\n4x - (-4) \u003d -8\n4x + 4 \u003d -84x \u003d -8 - 4 \u003d -12\nx \u003d -12 / 4 \u003d -3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x - y \u003d -8\n4x \u003d -12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-5, 4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(x - 2y) \u003d 3(-13)\n3x - 6y \u003d -39\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-2y \u003d -8\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -8 / -2 \u003d 4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x - 4y \u003d -31\n3x - 4(4) \u003d -31\n3x + -16 \u003d -31\n3x \u003d -31 + 16 \u003d -15\nx \u003d -15 / 3 \u003d -5", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx - 2y \u003d -13\n3x - 4y \u003d -31", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, 2)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\nx + y \u003d 11\nx + 3y \u003d 7-2y \u003d -4\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -4 / -2 \u003d 2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\nx + 5y \u003d 11\nx + 5(2) \u003d 11\nx + 10 \u003d 11x \u003d 11 - 10 \u003d 1\nx \u003d 1 / 1 \u003d 1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + 5y \u003d 11\nx + 3y \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, 2)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 5\n5(3x + 4y) \u003d 5(20)\n15x + 20y \u003d 100\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n19y \u003d 38\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 38 / 19 \u003d 2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n15x + y \u003d 62\n15x + (2) \u003d 62\n15x + 2 \u003d 62\n15x \u003d 62 - 2 \u003d 60\nx \u003d 60 / 15 \u003d 4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 4y \u003d 20\n15x + y \u003d 62", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, 4)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n3x + 3y \u003d 16\n3x + 4y \u003d 283y \u003d 12\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 12 / 3 \u003d 4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x + y \u003d 16\n3x + (4) \u003d 16\n3x + 4 \u003d 163x \u003d 16 - 4 \u003d 12\nx \u003d 12 / 3 \u003d 4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + y \u003d 16\n3x + 4y \u003d 28", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, -1)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(2x + 4y) \u003d 4(-2)\n8x + 16y \u003d -8\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n19y \u003d -19\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -19 / 19 \u003d -1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n8x - 3y \u003d 11\n8x - 3(-1) \u003d 11\n8x + 3 \u003d 11\n8x \u003d 11 - 3 \u003d 8\nx \u003d 8 / 8 \u003d 1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 4y \u003d -2\n8x - 3y \u003d 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-4, 2)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, y:\n-2x + 3y \u003d 10\n3x + y \u003d -105x \u003d -20\nSolve for x in thenew equation\nx \u003d -20 / 5 \u003d -4\nFind the value of y by plugging in the value for x into one of the original equations\n-2x + y \u003d 10\n-2(-4) + y \u003d 10\ny + 8 \u003d 10\ny \u003d 10 - 8 \u003d 2\ny \u003d 2 / 1 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-2x + y \u003d 10\n3x + y \u003d -10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, -1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n3x + 3y \u003d 1\n3x + 8y \u003d -56y \u003d -6\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d -6 / 6 \u003d -1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x + 2y \u003d 1\n3x + 2(-1) \u003d 1\n3x + -2 \u003d 13x \u003d 1 + 2 \u003d 3\nx \u003d 3 / 3 \u003d 1", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + 2y \u003d 1\n3x + 8y \u003d -5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(0, 1)", "explanation": "Subtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable, x\n-x - y \u003d 1\n-x + 2y \u003d 21y \u003d 1\nSolve for y in the new equation\ny \u003d 1 / 1 \u003d 1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n-x + y \u003d 1\n-x + (1) \u003d 1\n-x + 1 \u003d 1-x \u003d 1 - 1 \u003d 0\nx \u003d 0 / -1 \u003d 0", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-x + y \u003d 1\n-x + 2y \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, 3)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(4x + 3y) \u003d 3(17)\n12x + 9y \u003d 51\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n8y \u003d 24\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 24 / 8 \u003d 3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n12x + y \u003d 27\n12x + (3) \u003d 27\n12x + 3 \u003d 27\n12x \u003d 27 - 3 \u003d 24\nx \u003d 24 / 12 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x + 3y \u003d 17\n12x + y \u003d 27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3, 1)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(2x + 4y) \u003d 3(10)\n6x + 12y \u003d 30\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n13y \u003d 13\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 13 / 13 \u003d 1\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n6x - y \u003d 17\n6x - (1) \u003d 17\n6x + -1 \u003d 17\n6x \u003d 17 + 1 \u003d 18\nx \u003d 18 / 6 \u003d 3", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n2x + 4y \u003d 10\n6x - y \u003d 17", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2, 2)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 2\n2(3x + y) \u003d 2(-4)\n6x + 2y \u003d -8\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n7y \u003d 14\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 14 / 7 \u003d 2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n6x - 5y \u003d -22\n6x - 5(2) \u003d -22\n6x + -10 \u003d -22\n6x \u003d -22 + 10 \u003d -12\nx \u003d -12 / 6 \u003d -2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n3x + y \u003d -4\n6x - 5y \u003d -22", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(0, 3)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 4\n4(4x - 2y) \u003d 4(-6)\n16x - 8y \u003d -24\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-3y \u003d -9\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -9 / -3 \u003d 3\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n16x - 5y \u003d -15\n16x - 5(3) \u003d -15\n16x + -15 \u003d -15\n16x \u003d -15 + 15 \u003d 0\nx \u003d 0 / 16 \u003d 0", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n4x - 2y \u003d -6\n16x - 5y \u003d -15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2, -4)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by 3\n3(x + 4y) \u003d 3(-14)\n3x + 12y \u003d -42\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n10y \u003d -40\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d -40 / 10 \u003d -4\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x + 2y \u003d -2\n3x + 2(-4) \u003d -2\n3x + -8 \u003d -2\n3x \u003d -2 + 8 \u003d 6\nx \u003d 6 / 3 \u003d 2", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\nx + 4y \u003d -14\n3x + 2y \u003d -2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-4, -2)", "explanation": "Get one of the variables to have the same coefficient in both equations\nMultiply the first equation by -3\n-3(-x + y) \u003d -3(2)\n3x - 3y \u003d -6\nSubtract the two equations from each other to eliminate the variable x\n-8y \u003d 16\nSolve for \u0027y\u0027 in the new equation\ny \u003d 16 / -8 \u003d -2\nFind the value of x by plugging in the value for y into one of the original equations\n3x + 5y \u003d -22\n3x + 5(-2) \u003d -22\n3x + -10 \u003d -22\n3x \u003d -22 + 10 \u003d -12\nx \u003d -12 / 3 \u003d -4", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Solve for x and y by elimination:\n-x + y \u003d 2\n3x + 5y \u003d -22", "type": "text"}
]}